https://www.cnb-brownwood.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Citizens National Bank:
Ph: (325) 643-3545
eMail:
OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
Your relationship with us is important and we know that respect for your privacy is the very foundation of that relationship. Since our company was founded, we have built a relationship based on trust. Advances in technology have made safeguarding private information all the more important. Along with our promise to provide you financial services, we promise to safeguard the information you share with us.
ABOUT THIS PRIVACY NOTICE
This notice tells you important information. It describes Citizens National Bank’s privacy policy including how we collect, use and safeguard customer information.
Click here for our Privacy Notice
Keeping You Up To Date
We will provide you with a copy of our privacy notice at account opening and when we make material changes.
If you have any questions about our privacy notice , please contact us.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
The Federal Trade Commission’s Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) requires that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.
Contacting Citizens National Bank about this Web Site
Citizens National Bank
1 Carnegie
Brownwood, Texas 76801
Phone: (325) 643-3545
Email: ibdept@cnb-brownwood.com
Electronic mail is not necessarily secure. You should be very cautious when sending electronic mail containing sensitive, confidential information. As an alternative, you should consider sending it by postal mail.
SECURITY NOTICE
Please be advised that Citizens National Bank will never request confidential information through an e-mail request. If you receive any such e-mail, please contact us at the number or email listed above.
LOCATIONS Citizens National Bank
#1 Carnegie St.,
P.O. Box 1629,
Brownwood, Texas 76804
325-643-3545
Citizens National Bank – Walmart Branch
401 W Commerce St,.
